

Experienced Software Developer seeking roles in Software Development related to Technologies like HTML5,CSS,JavaScript,C,C++,Java,AngularJS,Python,Tensorflow.



Current Designation: Solution Consultant Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 3 Month(s)

Current Company: Apisero Inc. Notice Period: 3 Months

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project

Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution

Architecture, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, C, C++, Java, Angular JS, Python, Tensorflow, Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

# Summary

I am a result-oriented enthusiastic Professional with over 2+ years of experience in Software Development who continuously craves learning new things in Computer Science and willing to utilize my skills in the bestpossible way to solve professional problems of the organization where I would work.

Technologies I am well acquainted with are HTML5,CSS,JavaScript,C,C++,Java,AngularJS,Python,Reactjs.

## **Work Experience**

Apisero Inc. as Solution Consultant

Nov 2020 to Till Date

Mulesoft Development

#### Siemens Digital Industries Software as Software Developer -Java

Feb 2019 to Nov 2020

Achievements/Tasks

Products Worked On: Teamcenter, Active Workspace Technologies Used: C, C++, Java, Javascript, HTML, CSS Frameworks: Appolo (Siemens Proprietary), AngularJS Development: Worked on enhancing the PLM products and

fixing their defects

#### **HCL Technologies** as Software Engineer

Aug 2018 to Jan 2019

Achievements/Tasks

Worked on Siemens PLM Products.

Technologies used : C/C++, Java, HTML, CSS, Javascript. Worked on Teamcenter ITK,SOA Customization, BMIDE and

Active Workspace Client Customization.

### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Shri Guru Gobind Singhji College of Engineering and technology, Nanded in 2018

### **IT Skills**

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
HTML5, CSS	
JavaScript	
C, C++	
JAVA	
AngularJs	
Python	
TensorFlow	
Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib	
REACT	

## **Languages Known**

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

### **Affirmative Action**

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

### **Work Authorization**

US Work Status: Need H1 Visa

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time